https://www.tabcorp.com.au/privacy

Who We Are
Our Vision and PurposeOur BrandsOur LeadersCorporate Governance
Corporate Responsibility
CommunityWorkplaceGovernanceResponsible EntertainmentEnvironment
Investors
Shareholder ServicesAnnual ReportsAnnual General MeetingPresentationsPerformance SummaryCalendarEntitlement Offer
Purpose
This summary of the Tabcorp Group privacy policy provides an overview of how we collect, store and use the personal information that we receive or create about you. Personal information includes information about someone who is identified or reasonably identifiable, such as their name, address or date of birth. Tabcorp is bound by the Privacy Act and the Australian Privacy Principles. As this document is only a summary of the Tabcorp Group privacy policy, you should read the full policy for complete details of how we collect, store and use your personal information.
Who the policy applies to
The Tabcorp Group privacy policy applies to all of the companies that form part of the Tabcorp Group within Australia.
Acceptance of privacy policy
By using any Tabcorp website or product, agreeing to the terms and conditions of any Tabcorp account, providing services to Tabcorp, or otherwise providing your personal information to us, you agree to our privacy policy. We may make changes to the privacy policy and these changes will take effect when uploaded on our websites or apps. Your ongoing use of our products and services indicates that you accept the changes.
What information does Tabcorp collect and hold?
The kind of information we collect and hold about you depends on the nature of your dealings with us and the requirements of applicable laws, regulations, licence conditions and betting rules. We may collect, for example:
your name, date of birth, email address, mobile telephone number and other contact details, as well as copies of documents confirming your identity, such as your driver’s licence, passport or utility bills;
your gender, credit card or bank account details, lifestyle or betting frequency details, details of your online behaviour and recordings of phone calls between you and us;
information about our shareholders, including bank account details, security holder identification number and tax file number or ABN exemption;
footage from video surveillance at our retail agencies, venues and other sites;
information about staff of our retail venues including name, address, age, position, citizenship/migration/visa status, copies of pay slips, rosters, and proof of wage/superannuation payments;
your qualifications, experience, employment history, salary expectations and other information if you wish to be employed or engaged (directly or indirectly) by us;
background information such as your criminal record and whether you are a politically exposed or sanctioned person, if you wish to be employed or engaged (directly or indirectly) by us or are one of our suppliers or customers (or are employed or engaged by them); and
details of your qualifications and your citizenship, Aboriginal or Torres Strait Islander origin and any disability you have if you enrol for a Tabcorp training program.
How we collect personal information
We'll usually collect information from you directly, via our websites or apps, over the telephone or in person. We may collect information from a third party if it isn't reasonable or practical to collect it from you or if required by law.
For example, we may collect your personal information from:
third parties that can help assess your risk to our business under the Anti-Money Laundering and Counter-Terrorism Financing Act 2006 (Cth);
your employer if you’re employed by a company that supplies products or services to us;
our related bodies corporate;
our share registry provider;
our retail venues;
any entity that provides training consultancy services to us;
public sources (e.g. social media sites, Google and other websites); and
regulatory bodies and any other government authorities or agencies.
Why we collect and hold personal information
We may collect and hold your personal information to:
identify you and verify your identity;
manage the products and services we provide to you;
market our, and our related companies', products and services to you and enable them and selected third party partners to market to you;
comply with our responsible gambling commitments;
administer and manage the ownership of Tabcorp shares;
consider you for employment, if you apply for a position with us;
do business with our suppliers of goods and services;
develop and improve our products and services;
maintain security of accounts and venues;
assist retail venues in their management activities;
protect our rights and property and those of any Tabcorp customer; and
satisfy any other purpose required or permitted by law.
If we’re unable to collect your personal information, we may not be able to provide products and services to you.
How we use and disclose personal information
We may disclose your personal information to, for example:
our employees, contractors and service providers, to perform their jobs or provide their services;
sports controlling bodies, regulators and any other relevant commonwealth, state and territory government authorities and agencies;
our retail venues;
our related companies, so they can comply with their obligations under laws, licence conditions and betting rules and can directly market to you;
credit reporting bodies and others, to verify your identity as required by anti-money laundering and counter-terrorism financing laws (by agreeing to this policy, you consent for us to share certain personal information with credit reporting bodies. Please see our privacy policy for details about this);
our business partners and other third parties if you join a Tabcorp loyalty program, so they can send you offers and information about their products and services; and/or
another business, if we transfer provision of a product/service to that business, or stop providing a product/service and that business offers a similar product/service.
We may also use and disclose your personal information:
for audit, market-research and internal training purposes;
as necessary to protect any person or our rights or property; or
for marketing purposes, including contacting you via email, SMS, MMS, phone calls, direct mail or any other means to send you information on behalf of us or third parties, and to enable our related companies and selected third-party partners to provide you product and service information directly. Your consent to this will last indefinitely (including after your Tabcorp account(s) is closed) unless you opt-out.
Security of personal information
Tabcorp takes privacy seriously and takes reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from misuse, interference, loss and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.
How to contact us about your personal information
You can ask for access to, or to correct, personal information we hold about you, or make a privacy complaint, by contacting the Privacy Officer at:
Level 21, Tower 2, 727 Collins Street, Docklands, VIC 3008
Telephone: +61 3 9868 2890 or email: privacy@tabcorp.com.au
Disclosure of personal information overseas
We may disclose your personal information to recipients located outside Australia that provide, among other things, customer relationship management, identification and fraud detection, cloud and data storage, IT support and/or other third-party services to us (for example, to third parties in the USA, United Kingdom, Japan, Ireland and India).
How long do we keep your personal information?
Once we no longer need to use or disclose your personal information and we are not legally required to keep that information, then we will take reasonable steps to destroy your personal information or to ensure it is de-identified.
Requests for Information
Tabcorp takes its obligations under the Privacy Act, and its commitment to its customers under our Privacy Policy, very seriously.
As a result, Tabcorp cannot release customer information unless a customer consents to the release or it is legally compelled to do so.
From time to time Tabcorp receives subpoenas from law firms, or members of the public and other interested parties.
In order for Tabcorp to respond to the subpoena, the Tabcorp entity which is the subject of the subpoena must be correct. If the person of interest holds an account with a Tabcorp group entity it will be with one (or more) of:
Wagering
Tab Limited (the NSW licensee)
Tabcorp Wagering (Vic) Pty Ltd (the Victorian licensee)
Tabcorp ACT Pty Ltd (the ACT licensee)
Ubet Qld Limited (the QLD licensee)
Ubet Tas Pty Ltd (the TAS licensee)
Ubet NT Pty Ltd (the NT licensee)
Ubet SA Pty Ltd (the SA licensee)
Lotteries
Golden Casket Lottery Corporation Limited (QLD, TAS* and NT*)
New South Wales Lotteries Corporation Pty Ltd (NSW and ACT)
Tattersall's Sweeps Pty Ltd (VIC and TAS)
Tatts Lotteries SA Pty Ltd (SA)
Tatts NT Lotteries Pty Ltd (NT)
* Instant Scratch-Its only
Due to privacy reasons, we are unable to disclose whether the person of interest holds an account with one or more of these entities.
Subpoenas should therefore be served on the appropriate company or, if the appropriate company is not known, all such entities. In the latter case, there is no need for separate subpoenas for each entity.
While correspondence regarding subpoenas should be sent to the following address, the subpoena itself should be served on each of the above entities.
Alternatively, please email any correspondence to requestforinfo@tabcorp.com.au
